



Afghanistan, Herat, Jebraiel Herat, 3001



+93780649493, +93795931789



sahebiitsupptech@gmail.com

# Mahmood Sahebi

**Dear Armis-Tech Company** 

25-May -2023

## Dear sir/madam

I am interested in applying for the vacancy in your organization as **web developer**. I feel qualified for the vacancy based on my experience and education.

I want to employ all my expertise and experience in delivering best service to your institution and through it to the community.

To further acquaint you with the specifics of my background I am enclosing my resume. I hope you will consider me for this position. I have completed computer science in NIMA (National Institute of Management & Administration) Kabul, working as junior technical Engineer about 1.5 year at Mikrogate ICT, and in addition, I have completed various courses related to web programming which would be an extra asset for your organization.

I have taught English and computer programs in different courses at Herat and Kabul and I had private classes and invested in them, taught English and computer about 4 year and assisted many poor families & students with course fees.

I have mentioned my junior **Mr. Ramazan Ali Hasanzadah** as **NOC Engineer II at** Mikrogate ICT as reference at end of my resume.

If you are interested in meeting with me. I am available for interview.

I look forward hearing from you.

Sincerely yours Mahmood Sahebi



## **Mahmood Sahebi**

Herat, Afghanistan • +93-780649493/+93-795931789 • • sahebiitsupptech@gmail.com



## ▼ Objective

As I said that I have graduated from computer science – Kabul NIMA. And I have experience of 3 years teaching English and about 1 year of teaching computer programs. I have passed special class of ICDL, as I am working in ICT about 1.5 year, having knowledge in troubleshooting local network problems, using computer programs and windows operating system and I also do programming (web development), I am committed to give my best for the organization I will be supposed to work for loyalty, punctuality and honesty are what truly trust in my work areas.

### Education

- Associated Degree in ICT National Institute of Management and administration (NIMA), the only accredited institute in byy ACBSP & IITB Kabul, Afghanistan. (2020)
- Certify from Ball State University of America in English language. (2019)
- Graduated 12<sup>th</sup> Grade Jebraeil High School Herat-Afghanistan. (2014)
- Completed ICDL classes through Help NGO. (2011)
- Completed English American Headway at CH.M.C.E.A (Churda Massum Cultural Educational Association). (2007)

## Experience

### 2022-2023

• Employee at Mikrogate ICT as Technical Engineer, Herat-Afghanistan.

#### 2021-2022

Taught Computer programs (had private Classes self-invested).

#### 2021-2022

Taught computer programs at Tahlil Garan Academy, Herat Jebraiel.

#### 2019-2020

• Taught English at Tamaddon Academy, Kabul-Afghanistan.

## 2010-2012.

Taught English at CH.M.C.E.A (Churda Massum Cultural Educational Association), Herat- Jebraiel.

## **Mahmood Sahebi**

Herat, Afghanistan • +93-780649493/+93-795931789 • sahebiitsupptech@gmail.com



#### 2021-2022

- Taught computer programs at Tahlil Garan Academy, Herat Jebraiel.
  - o Taught FCC (Fundamental of Computer concepts), windows, office packages.
  - o Had presented seminars about scholarships and the way how to register them.

### 2019-2020

- Taught English at Tamaddon Academy, Kabul-Afghanistan.
  - o Taught Let's go system for beginners & American English File system for intermediate students.
  - o Conduct different exams for each and every level at the end of each course and level.

#### 2010-2012.

- Taught English at CH.M.C.E.A (Churda Massum Cultural Educational Association), Herat- Jebraiel.
  - o Taught Let's go systems & streamline system.
  - Conduct different exams for each level and book and had many graduations and signed many certificates. I have mentions my appreciation letters as prove in my resume.

## Network skills

## Assignments and accomplished tutorials:

NIMA (National Institute of Management and Administration) Assignments

Kabul-Darul-Aman, Afghanistan

- Configuring simple and advanced CISCO routers & Switches protocols (Ether Channel, and VLANs).
- Scenarios on university CISCO laboratory.
- Configuring and troubleshooting CCNA on university laboratory and powerful simulation software (Packet tracer).

## Accomplished free and purchased tutorials

 Watched and learned several tutorials on MCSA Windows Server 2016 (Active Directory, DHCP, DNS, Watched tutorial on CompTIA A+, Network+, & MTCNA..

## **Mahmood Sahebi**

Herat, Afghanistan • +93-780649493/+93-795931789 • sahebiitsupptech@gmail.com



## Network skills

## Assignments and accomplished tutorials:

NIMA (National Institute of Management and Administration) Assignments Kabul-Darul-Aman, Afghanistan

- Configuring simple and advanced CISCO routers & Switches protocols (Ether Channel, and VLANs).
- Scenarios on university CISCO laboratory.
- Configuring and troubleshooting CCNA on university laboratory and powerful simulation software (Packet tracer).

### Accomplished free and purchased tutorials

• Watched and learned several tutorials on MCSA Windows Server 2016 (Active Directory, DHCP, DNS, Watched tutorial on CompTIA A+, Network+, & MTCNA..

#### References

• Ramazan Ali Hasanzadah

NOC Engineer II at Mikrogate ICT

E-mail: Ramazanali.l2015@gmail.com

#:+93 794084787

#:+93 786596692

· Parag Rabade

HOD - ICT department of National Institute of Management and Administration (NIMA), Kabul Afghanistan and Former project manager at Microsoft company.

E-mail: rparag2112@gmail.com

Mohammad Yasir Hakmi

ICT Department Coordinator of (NIMA),

Kabul-Afghanistan.

E-mail: hakimi.att@gmail.com

#: +93 (0)772010213

• Ms.Wazhma

Instructor and Intern-supervisor at NIMA, Kabul-Afghanistan.

E-mail: a.wazhma@yahoo.com